Saahib Mohammed, Software Developer

 $Columbus, United \, States, 6143164611, robotics saahib@gmail.com$

LINKS	Github, Linkedn			
PROFILE	As a recent Ohio State University graduate with a focus on front-end web development, I am a software developassionate about technology. My experience includes participating in hackathons and working with technolog like JavaScript, React, and GCP. I am dedicated to honing my skills and contributing to any team. My role a Apple and my time at Riverside Education Center have equipped me with a unique blend of skills. Addition as an entry-level data analyst and software developer, I hold certifications in the Google Data Analyst and M Front End programs, further enriching my professional profile.			
SKILLS	Communication Skills	Expert	JavaScript	Experience
	SQL	Skillful	C programing	Beginne
	Customer Service	Expert	Firebase	Skillfu
	Microsoft Office	Skillful	React	Skillfu
	Node.js	Experienced	Openrefine	Beginne
	Git	Skillful	MongoDB	Skillfu
	Java	Experienced	Firebase	Exper
	HTML & CSS	Experienced	Tailwind css	Exper
	Python	Skillful	Next js	Exper
	Software Logic	Skillful	Java	Exper
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Apr 2020	 Teacher, Riverside Education Center With three years of experience in early STEM childhood education Created countless hands-on activities that help children explore and understand key STEM concepts. Monitored and reported student progress to the teacher, providing feedback on areas of improvement Also developed a site to improve sales and get more people to enroll at out center improving enrollment by almost 50% 			
Sep 2023 — Jan 2024	 Specialist, Apple Informed customers about different types of products they wanted to use Help customers find products that are used daily Help customers set up any product they might have trouble with Gave customers suggestions about products they would benefit from 			Columbu
EDUCATION				
Aug 2017 — May 2020	High school diploma, Worthington Killbourne			Columbu
Tiug 2017 — Way 2020	Associates Degree, Ohio State University			
,	Associates Degree, Ohio S	State University		Columbu
Aug 2020 — Present	Associates Degree, Ohio S Certification, OpenClass	•		
Aug 2020 — Present	Ç	rooms	ıpervised Machine model, and ι	Columbu
Aug 2020 — Present May 2023 — May 2023 Sep 2023 — Present	Certification, OpenClass	rooms	ıpervised Machine model, and ι	Columbu

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Jan 2016 — Present Freelance web development

made sites for clothing brands (kwhys and Jah's) and Riverside education centers which they are now implementing now